Section B, Activity 2B. Read the following letter.
Underline the subjects you May likes.
Circle the subjects she doesn't like.
Are you May's ideas the same as yours?
Dear Jenny, I am very busy on Friday.
At 8, I have math. It is not fun.
The teacher says it is useful, but I think it is difficult.
Then at 9, I have science. It is difficult,
but interesting.
At 10, I have history. After that,
I have P.E. at 11. It is easy and fun.
Lunch is from 12 to 1, and after that,
we have Chinese. It is my favorite subject.
Our Chinese teacher, Mrs. Wang,
is great fun.
My class is finished at 1.50, but after that,
I have an art lesson for two hours. It is really relaxing.
How about you? When are your classes?
What is your favorite subject?
Your friend, you May.